<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Birmingham on Adrian de Lima | Musician</title>
    <link>http://AdriandeLima.github.io/tags/birmingham/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Birmingham on Adrian de Lima | Musician</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://AdriandeLima.github.io/tags/birmingham/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Moon River</title>
      <link>http://AdriandeLima.github.io/blog/2025-08-29-moon-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://AdriandeLima.github.io/blog/2025-08-29-moon-river/</guid>
      <description>Moon River composed by Henry Mancini with lyrics by Johnny Mercer, here arranged by Denny Wang and performed by Adrian de Lima and Toby Baker.
We performed this piece to celebrate graduating from the University of Birmingham, featuring the university&amp;rsquo;s iconic clock tower Old Joe playing the role of the moon.
I hope you enjoy!
Socials:
/adriandelima.music https://adriandelima.github.io/ @AdriandelimaMusic @tobyb1506 @nicolegisbourne Lyrics:
Moon river, wider than a mile I&amp;#39;m crossing you in style someday (Someday, day) A dream maker (Maker, maker) My heartbreaker (You heartbreaker) Wherever you&amp;#39;re goin&amp;#39;, I&amp;#39;m goin&amp;#39; that way (The same, the same) Two drifters off to see the world There&amp;#39;s such a crazy world to see We&amp;#39;re all chasin&amp;#39; after all the same Chasin&amp;#39; after our ends Moon river, wider than a mile Crossin&amp;#39; in style someday My dream maker, heartbreaker Wherever you&amp;#39;re goin&amp;#39;, I&amp;#39;m goin&amp;#39; the same Two drifters off to see the world It&amp;#39;s such a crazy world, you&amp;#39;ll see (What I see, who I become) (What I see, who I become) We&amp;#39;re all chasin&amp;#39; after our ends Chasin&amp;#39; after our ends Life&amp;#39;s just around the bend, my friend Moon river and me Featured Comments Many thanks to all those who helped me put this one together, Toby, Nicole, Tevin, Noa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wylde Green Concert</title>
      <link>http://AdriandeLima.github.io/blog/2025-08-04-wylde-green-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://AdriandeLima.github.io/blog/2025-08-04-wylde-green-concert/</guid>
      <description>An evening of concert featuring Lalo &amp;amp; Bridge by Adrian de Lima and Toby Baker at Wylde Green United Reformed Church.
On 16th Feb 2025, I performed a selection of minatures by Frank Bridge, and Lalo&amp;rsquo;s Symphony Espagnole, at Wylde Green United Reformed Church. Many thanks to all who came to support, to my accompanist, colleague and friend Toby Baker, and the team at Wylde Green and UoB Music, for the opportunity to put on this programme, we had an awesome time!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
